The story of the war at home, and the people who lived through it.
Gardens of Stone is a war, drama, history film directed by Francis Ford Coppola.
At Arlington National Cemetery during the Vietnam era, veteran sergeant Clell
Hazard trains young soldiers while mourning those lost in combat.
Unable to return to war himself, he mentors Jackie Willow—the idealistic son of a fallen
comrade—hoping to prepare him for the realities of Vietnam and the cost of duty.
Sgt. Clell Hazard, played by James Caan.
Samantha Davis, played by Anjelica Huston.
Sgt. Maj.'Goody' Nelson, played by James Earl Jones.
Jackie Willow, played by D. B. Sweeney.
Capt. Homer Thomas, played by Dean Stockwell.
Rachel Feld, played by Mary Stuart Masterson.
Gardens of Stone is a 1987 American drama film directed by Francis Ford
Coppola, based on a 1983 novel of the same name by Nicholas Proffitt.
It stars James Caan, Anjelica Huston, James Earl Jones, D.
Sweeney, Dean Stockwell and Mary Stuart Masterson.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, vietnam veteran,
washington dc, usa, cemetery, soldier.
The tone is emotional.